var jsonAnatomy = `{
  "id": 104,
  "title": "Anatomy",
  "clues": [{
      "id": 5000,
      "answer": "Bladder",
      "question": "A stretchable, membranous sac that temporarily holds urine secreted by the kidneys",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 103,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5001,
      "answer": "Uterus",
      "question": "The internal organ where the unborn fetus is developed",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5002,
      "answer": "Mandible",
      "question": "The name for the lower jawbone",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5003,
      "answer": "Navicular bone",
      "question": "The small, flat bone that lies within the hoof",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5004,
      "answer": "Ankle",
      "question": "Another name for the fetlock joint",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5005,
      "answer": "7",
      "question": "The number of cervical vertebrae in a horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5006,
      "answer": "Crest",
      "question": "The correct name for the curved upper part of the horse's neck",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5007,
      "answer": "Withers",
      "question": "the name of the highest point of the horse's shoulders that is defined as the bony protrusion between the neck and the back",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5008,
      "answer": "Hock",
      "question": "The common name for the tarsal joint",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5009,
      "answer": "Liver",
      "question": "The horses largest gland",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5010,
      "answer": "Molars",
      "question": "These teeth are used for grinding",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5011,
      "answer": "Hoof",
      "question": "This part of the horse is made up of the top, quarter, and heel",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5012,
      "answer": "205",
      "question": "Total number of bones in the horse skeleton",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5013,
      "answer": "2",
      "question": "The number of kidneys a horse has",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5014,
      "answer": "Pastern",
      "question": "The common term for the area between the fetlock and coronet on a horseâ€™s leg",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5015,
      "answer": "Kidney",
      "question": "Organ that provides a blood-filtering system that is responsible for the removal of many waste products from the body",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5016,
      "answer": "Liver",
      "question": "The organ of the horse that produces bile",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5017,
      "answer": "Frog",
      "question": "During the horseshoeing process, the horseshoe is centered on a normal foot by using the apex of this part of the hoof as guide",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5018,
      "answer": "Ligaments",
      "question": "Bands of fibrous tissue that attaches bones to bones",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5019,
      "answer": "Mouth",
      "question": "The first part of the digestive system",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5020,
      "answer": "6",
      "question": "The number of joints in the foreleg of the horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5021,
      "answer": "Poll",
      "question": "The bony prominence that lies between the ears of the horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5022,
      "answer": "Frog",
      "question": "This part of a horses foot absorbs concussion",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5023,
      "answer": "Pancreas",
      "question": "This organ produces insulin which controls glucose levels in the horses body",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5024,
      "answer": "Knee",
      "question": "What is a common name for the carpus joint",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 5025,
      "answer": "Knee",
      "question": "The forces exerted by muscles in the distal foreleg are transmitted by tendons. Generally muscles are not found below this joint of the foreleg",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 104,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    }
  ]
}`;
